

# Business Analyst ~ 3 moe <u>£</u> 22/02/1999 **DUONG NGUYEN** O MBTI: INFJ

. 0946 292 494

O District 10, HCM City.

**∇**<sup>•</sup> duongnguyen.22@icloud.com

(a) darleigh.com | LinkedIn

### **Brief introduce**

I genuinely want to use technology in my life to increase efficiency and provide long-term benefit for society. I believe that I have the qualities necessary to succeed. These qualities are demonstrated by my academic and extracurricular experiences.

## **Education**

Bachelors, Ton Duc Thang University. (2017-Expect 2023)

**Software Engineering, GPA 7.2/10.** 

Class director: Good Rating. Spiritual unity among 87 classmates to grow together in knowledge and common activities.

### +46 Certifications

**IIBA Business Analyst Foundations** Communicate

Presentation **Google Project Management** 

Critical Thinking Google UX Designer

Problem Analysis **Google Analytics** 

**Decision-making** Google IT Python

Negotiation **IIG TOEIC R&L 530** 

**Agile Foundations** Google Digital Marketing 9LX 7AB 5MF

# **Experience**

BlockchainWork (10/2022-11/2022)

Digital Solution R&D • Webframe • Agile

In charge of current web3 product research and development, which includes:

- Analyze superiors' requirements and provide solutions to challenges.
- Create function for website to manage stakeholder and enhance user experience UIX.
- Describe the system's SRS document.

**Luong Thanh Phat Company** (05/2022 - 08/2022)

**Techinical Collaborator** • Django • Waterfall

Web applications provide digital transformation and processization of contract administration, enhanced tram information, and car rental partners using software.

HongHanh Wedding Services (05/2022 - Present)

**Technical Co-Founder** • Product Designer • Sales • Leadership • Waterfall

Applying digital transformation involves the use of cloud technologies in task management and work assignment to other jobs. Furthermore, self-employment allows me to better grasp the duties and processes involved in optimizing the efficiency of overtime labor.

Jobnet Vietnam (10/2020-02/2021)

**UIX Designer Intern · Visual Designer · Webapp** 

In this employment, I was taught in fundamental programming abilities and website expertise, storing data about websites such as LandingPage, eCommerce.